export const jokes = [
  {
    id: 0,
    question: "Which weather features do druggies like most??",
    answer: "Highs"
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "Why do mother kangaroos hate rainy days?",
    answer: "Because then the children have to play inside."
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Why do hurricanes travel so fast?",
    answer:
      "Because if they travelled slowly, we’d have to call them slow-i-canes."
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Jill: How did you find the weather on your vacation?",
    answer: "Bill: I just went outside and there it was!"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is hail?",
    answer: "Hard boiled rain!"
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Who is it that everybody listens to but nobody believes?",
    answer: "The weatherman."
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Fred: I’m sure I’m right.",
    answer: "Betty: You’re as right as rain – all wet!"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "Gosh, it’s raining cats and dogs, said Fred looking out of the kitchen window.",
    answer: "“I know,” said his mother. “I’ve just stepped in a poodle!”"
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "How did the hail stone describe it’s life?",
    answer: "It really has a lot of ups and downs"
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What are the hottest days during summer?",
    answer: "Sun-days"
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "If a band plays music in a thunderstorm, who is most likely to get hit by lightning?",
    answer: "The conductor."
  }
];
